[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Badgers like to use one den all year round.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rory Calhoun was the star of The Texan, a weekly western series that ran on CBS.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which US state is the Bicycle Museum of America located?", "correct_answer": "Ohio", "incorrect_answers": ["Indiana", "Massachusetts", "North Carolina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The exprssion The dog days of summer  was first used because of this.", "correct_answer": "An astronomical idea", "incorrect_answers": ["A false idea about the effect of animals on the world", "A description of how dogs pant", "A superstition"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Narcissus is the birth flower of this month, and its birthstone is the aquamarine.", "correct_answer": "March", "incorrect_answers": ["July", "May", "October"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This phobia is known as the fear of criticism.", "correct_answer": "Enosiophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Ephebiphobia", "Entomophobia", "Eosophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gouda and Edam are famous types of Dutch cheeses.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On May 1, 2009, the three astronauts from Apollo 11 were granted this exceptional award.", "correct_answer": "Congressional Gold Medal", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Purple heart", "Presidential Medal of Freedom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jason has 3 quarters, 8 nickels, 6 dimes and 3 pennies. How much money does he have?", "correct_answer": "$1.78", "incorrect_answers": ["$0.35", "$2.58", "$1.93"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the difference between Felix and Oscar from the 1968 movie The Odd Couple?", "correct_answer": "Felix is a neatfreak, and Oscar is a pig.", "incorrect_answers": ["Oscar loves animals, and Felix loves hunting.", "Felix is a playboy, and Oscar is very shy.", "Oscar is wealthy, and Felix is dirt-poor."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these names does not refer to a sloth?", "correct_answer": "Rikki-Tikki-Tavi", "incorrect_answers": ["Ritto", "Rit", "Ridette"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Pursuit of Happyness, Alan Frakesh, the man who trained Chris, was played by what famous voice actor?", "correct_answer": "Dan Castellaneta", "incorrect_answers": ["Yeardly Smith", "Harry Shearer", "Hank Azaria"]}]